The neighborhood is changing…
Mulberry Street is a horror film directed by Jim Mickle.
A deadly infection breaks out in Manhattan, causing humans
to devolve into blood-thirsty rat creatures.
Six recently evicted tenants must survive the night and protect their downtown
apartment building as the city quickly spirals out of control.
Clutch, played by Nick Damici.
Ross, played by Tim House.
Peter Pace, played by Antone Pagán.
Charlie, played by Larry Fleischman.
Kay, played by Bo Corre.
Casey, played by Kim Blair.
Mulberry Street is a 2006 American horror film directed by Jim Mickle,
written by Nick Damici and Jim Mickle, and starring Nick Damici.
It was released by After Dark Films as a part of their 8 Films to Die For 2007.
The film explores themes of gore, infection, zombie, rat, giant rat.
The tone is dark.